Eslam A. Hugair

Junior MEAN stack Developer

Salah El deen St..
Gaza Strip
(+972) 592545262
e.eslam3bed@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Gaza Sky Geeks, Palestine — Quality Assurance, Team lead

06/2018 - 10/2018

I was responsible about making sure that every member in my team understands the application requirement, and implements them correctly.

Activat Startup, Palestine —CTO

03/2018 - 07/2018

I was taking CTO role in building an application that aims to bridge the gap between customers and service providers of activities and tours by providing a platform where users can customize their tours and activities, receive different deals, go through each offer, read reviews and approve the most suitable one, and now our CEO looking for investors and we are supported by a local startups accelerator.

University Of Palestine, Palestine — *Teaching Assistant*

09/2017 - 06/2018

Discuss and practice the abstract side of the Software Engineering materials, Ex, Programming, Data Structure, Software Architecture and networking in a practical way.

EDUCATION

University Of Palestine, Palestine—Bachelor degree

2012 - 2017

I have studied Software Engineering for five years in the university of Palestine ,and graduated first degree and I have been chosen to take a role as a teaching assistant for one year after.

SKILLS

Vanilla Javascript.
Reactjs(redux,mobx,context)
WebRtc,Socket.io
Nodejs
Express js
RestFul (design & implement)
SQL(postgres,mySql,oracle)
NoSql(mongodb)
Elasticsearch
AWS(s3.ec2,ecs,fargate)

STATEMENT

I Started my career officially before two years in javascript after struggling with Java, and since then I started to develop my skill set in the web industry, I'm passionate about what I build and I hope one day I contribute in building a billion dollar business.

LANGUAGES

- English
- Arabic

PROJECTS

Leadcart — Web application

A platform that provide its customers to create their own marketplaces and create and share products of their own, and with affiliation and coupons systems.

Zaino — Web application

A platform that intent to enhance the Adword customers user experience with the addition of a banners creator ,the customers create the campaigns they want and create the banner for the ads and schedule the launch time,and just set and watch their campaign statistics and performance .

Drop shipping consultant — *Chrome extension*

Doing reconnaissance and data scraping on certain websites for analysis reasons and provide an suggesting for the customers using it.

Acronymly — *Chrome extension*

Providing acronyms meaning relying on the acronyms context.